Guide to the Institute of Pacific Relations Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Part I: Cataloged Materials & the Pacific Council of the Institute of Pacific Relations
  - Part I.3 Uncataloged Office Files
    - Pacific Council of the Institute of Pacific Relations
      - 1943
        - Bajpai, Girja (Box 65)
        - Barnett, Robert W. (Box 65)
        - Be (Box 65)
        - Bi-Bl (Box 65)
        - Bisson, T.A. (Box 65)
        - Blow, Mary a (Box 65)
        - Bolton, Frances P. (Box 65)
        - Br (Box 65)
        - Bu (Box 65)
        - Buck, Pearl S. (Box 65)
        - Bunche, Ralph J. (Box 65)
        - C (Box 65)
        - Calkins, Robert D. (Box 65)
        - Canadian Institute of International Affairs (Box 65)
        - Carnegie Corporation (Box 66)
          - General (Box 66)
          - Jessup, Walter A. (Box 66)
        - The Misses Carter (Box 66)
        - Carter, Edward C.
          - General (Box 66)
          - Personal (Box 66)
          - Russia (Box 66)
        - Carter, Mrs. Edward C. (Box 66)
        - Carter, John Alden (Box 66)
        - Carter, Margaret T. (Box 66)
        - Carter, William D. (Box 66)
        - Century Association (Box 66)
        - Ch-Cl (Box 67)
        - China Institute of Pacific Relations (Box 67)
        - Chinese Intellectuals (Box 67)
        - Chow, S.R. (Box 67)
        - Collective Security (Box 67)
        - Condliffe, J.B.
          - General (Box 67)
          - Problems of Economic Reorganization (Box 67)
        - Conference Data Paper Revisions (Box 67)
        - Conference Pamphlet Ms. (Box 67)
        - Cooke, Dwight W. (Box 67)
        - Corbett, P.E. (Box 67)
        - Corn Exchange Bank (Box 67)
        - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 67)
        - Cr-Cu (Box 67)
        - Criticisms on Prospectus and 6 April Memo (Box 67)
        - Currie, Lauchlin (Box 67)
        - Da-De (Box 68)
        - Distribution Lists (Box 68)
        - Do (Box 68)
        - Downing, Elizabeth (Box 68)
        - E (Box 68)
        - East and West Association (Monthly Review) (Box 68)
        - Elizalde,J.M (Box 68)
        - Embree, Edwin R. (Box 68)
        - Emeny, Brooks (Box 68)
        - F (Box 68)
        - Fairfax-Chomeley, Elsie (Box 68)
        - Field, Frederick V. (Box 68)
        - Financial Statements, 1943 (Box 68)
        - Fong, H.D. (Box 68)
        - Foreign Policy Association (Box 68)
        - French Council (Box 68)
        - Furnivall, J.S. (Box 68)
        - G (Box 69)
        - Goodrich, Leland--World Peace Foundation (Box 69)
        - Grajdanzev, Andrew J. (Box 69)
        - Graves, Mortimer (Box 69)
        - Greenberg, Michael (Box 69)
        - Grover, Allen (Box 69)
        - H (Box 69)
        - Ha (Box 69)
        - Hallowell, Mrs, N. Penrose (Box 69)
        - He (Box 69)
        - Hi (Box 69)
        - Ho (Box 69)
        - Holland, W.L. (Box 69)
        - Holland, W.L.--Personal (Box 69)
        - Hornbeck, Stanley K. (Box 69)
        - Hsu, Y.Y.
          - Memo on Chinese Commodities Under Wartime Export Control (Box 69)
          - Notes on Chinese Clippings (Box 69)
        - Hu (Box 69)
        - I (Box 70)
        - India Princeton Conference, 1943 April 17
          - General (Box 70)
          - Agenda (Box 70)
          - Hotel Arrangements (Box 70)
        - IPR Notes (Transferred to IPR History)
        - IPR Round Table (Box 70)
        - International Air Force (Box 70)
        - Java Tiffin Club (Box 70)
        - Jayson, Alice (Box 70)
        - Jessup, Philip C. (Box 70)
        - Johnstone, William C. (Box 70)
        - Judd, Walter (Box 70)
        - K (Box 71)
        - Kennedy, Raymond (Box 71)
        - Khanna Meetings, 1943 January 22 and 24 (Box 71)
        - Ki-Ko (Box 71)
        - Ku (Box 71)
        - L (Box 71)
        - Lasker, Bruno (Box 71)
        - Lathan, H.S (Box 71)
        - Laurin, Pierre (Box 71)
        - Le (Box 71)
        - Lee, Rosamund (Box 71)
        - Li (Box 71)
        - Li, K.C. (Box 71)
        - Lin Yuen Hwa--The Golden Wing (Box 71)
        - Lingelbach, Willian E. (Box 71)
        - Litvinoff, Maxim (Box 71)
        - Lo-Ly (Box 71)
        - Lockwood, W.W. (Box 71)
        - Lockwood, W.W.--China Relief Project (Box 71)
        - Luce, Henry R. (Box 71)
        - Ma (Box 72)
        - Mayflower Hotel (Box 72)
        - Me (Box 72)
        - Me (Box 72)
        - Meng, Chih--China Institute in America (Box 72)
        - Mi (Box 72)
        - Mitchell, Kate L. (Box 72)
        - Mo-My (Box 72)
        - Moore, Harriet L. (Box 72)
        - N (Box 72)
        - Navy School (Box 72)
        - Normano, J.F. (Box 72)
        - O (Box 73)
        - Office of War Information (Box 73)
        - Pacific Council
          - General (6 Folders) (Box 73)
          - Agenda - Draft Administrative Program (Box 73)
          - Campaign Lists and Ideas (Box 73)
          - Financial Statements (Box 73)
          - Luncheon, 1943 February 13 (Box 73)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 73)
          - Pacific House (Box 73)
        - Packard, Arthur W. (Box 73)
        - Packard, Arthur W.--Appeal (Box 73)
        - Parker, Harriet Holmes (Box 74)
        - Parker, Philo W. (Box 74)
        - Parsons, Katrine W. (Box 74)
        - Philippine Conference - Washington, 1943 June 26-27 (Box 74)
        - Philippine Institute of International Affairs (Box 74)
        - Phillips, William (Box 74)
        - Pl-Pr (Box 74)
        - Porter, Catherine (Box 74)
        - Price, Harry B. (Box 74)
        - Program--IPR (Box 74)
        - R (Box 74)
        - Re (Box 74)
        - Relief Project (Box 74)
        - Research Projects (Box 74)
        - Research Reports (Box 74)
        - Ro (Box 74)
        - Rockefeller Foundation--Slavic Studies (Box 74)
        - Royal Institute of International Affairs
          - General (Box 74)
          - Macadam, Ivison (Box 74)
          - Cleeve, Margaret (Box 74)
        - Russian War Relief (Box 74)
        - S (Box 75)
        - St. Moritz Staff Meeting, 1943 March 19-20 (Box 75)
        - Sansom, George B. (Box 75)
        - Sch (Box 75)
        - Se (Box 75)
        - Semi-Official IPR Dates (Box 75)
        - Sh (Box 75)
        - Shridharani, Krishnalal (Box 75)
        - Si-Sl (Box 75)
        - Sm-Sp (Box 75)
        - Smith, Datus--Princeton University Press (Box 75)
        - Soong, T.V. (Box 75)
        - St (Box 75)
        - Staff Meetings (Box 75)
        - Stein, Guenther (Box 75)
        - Stevenson, James L. (Box 75)
        - Stewart, Marguerite A. (Box 75)
        - Su-Sz (Box 75)
        - T (Box 76)
        - Tarr, Edgar J. (Box 76)
        - Testimonials on Mt. Tremblant (Box 76)
        - Thomas, Elbert D. (Box 76)
        - To (Box 76)
        - Trippe, Juan (Box 76)
        - U (Box 76)
        - V (Box 76)
        - von Seebach, Hasso (Box 76)
        - Tarr, Edgar J. (Box 76)
        - Wa (Box 77)
        - Wallace, Schuyler--Columbia Navy School (Box 77)
        - Walsh, Richard J. (Box 77)
        - Washington, D.C.
          - Collective Security Meetings (Box 77)
          - Conference, 1943 October 9-10 (Box 77)
          - Meetings (with Photographs) (Box 77)
        - We (Box 77)
        - Weeks, David--Project: Utilization of China's Land and Water (Box 77)
        - Resources (Box 77)
        - Welles, Sumner (Box 77)
        - Wh-Wi (Box 77)
        - Willits, Joseph H. (Box 77)
        - Willkie, Wendell (Box 77)
        - Wo (Box 77)
        - Wood, Frederick H. (Box 77)
        - X-Y (Box 77)
        - Yale University Press (Box 77)
        - Yen, Y.R.C. James (Box 77)
        - Z (Box 77)
      - 1944
        - A (Box 78)
        - American Council
          - General (Box 78)
          - Board (Box 78)
          - Executive (Box 78)
          - Finance (Box 78)
        - An-Ay (Box 78)
        - Atlanta University (Box 78)
        - Austern, Hilda (Box 78)
        - Australian Institute of International Affairs (Box 78)
        - Ba (Box 78)
        - Bajpai, Girja Shankar (Box 78)
        - Barnett, Eugene E. (Box 78)
        - Barnett, Robert W. (Box 78)
        - Be (Box 78)
        - Bi-Bl (Box 78)
        - Bisson, T.A. (Box 78)
        - Bo (Box 78)
        - Bolton, Frances P. (Box 78)
        - Br (Box 78)
        - Bu (Box 78)
        - Buck, Pearl S. (Box 78)
        - Ca (Box 79)
        - Canadian Institute of International Affairs (Box 79)
        - Carnegie Corporation (Box 79)
        - The Misses Carter (Box 79)
        - Carter, Edward C.--Personal (Box 79)
        - Carter, Mrs. Edward C. (Box 79)
        - Carter, John A. (Box 79)
        - Carter, Margaret T. (Box 79)
        - Carter, Polly (Box 79)
        - Carter, William D. (Box 79)
        - Ce-Cl (Box 79)
        - Century Association (Box 79)
        - China Institute in America--Meng, Chih (Box 79)
        - China Institute of Pacific Relations (Box 79)
        - Claxton, Brooke (Box 79)
        - Co (Box 79)
        - Condliffe, J.B. (Box 79)
        - Conference Committee, 1945 (Box 79)
        - Coo (Box 80)
        - Corn Exchange Bank (Box 80)
        - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 80)
        - Cr (Box 80)
        - Da (Box 80)
        - De (Box 80)
        - Dennery, Etienne (Box 80)
        - Dennett, Raymond (Box 80)
        - Distribution Lists (Box 80)
        - Do (Box 80)
        - Dr-Dy (Box 80)
        - E (Box 80)
        - Elizalde, J.M. (Box 80)
        - Emeny, Brooks (Box 80)
        - En (Box 80)
        - Fa-Fe (Box 81)
        - Fairbank, Wilma (Box 81)
        - Fairfax-Chomeley, Elsie (Box 81)
        - Farley, Miriam S. (Box 81)
        - Faymonville, Philip R. (Box 81)
        - Fi (Box 81)
        - Financial Campaign - Million Dollar Fund (Box 81)
        - Fisher, Galen M. (Box 81)
        - Fo-Fu (Box 81)
        - Foreign Policy Association (Box 81)
        - French Committee Meeting (Box 81)
        - French I.P.R. Council (Box 81)
        - Ga (Box 81)
        - Ge (Box 81)
        - Gelfan, Harriet Moore (Box 81)
        - Gi-Go (Box 81)
        - Gr-Gu (Box 81)
        - Grajdanzev, Andrew J. (Box 81)
        - Grover, Allen (Box 81)
        - Ha (Box 82)
        - He (Box 82)
        - Healy, Mary F. (Box 82)
        - Hi (Box 82)
        - Ho (Box 82)
        - Holland, W.L. (Box 82)
        - Hornbeck, Stanley K. (Box 82)
        - Hsu, Y.Y. (Box 82)
        - Hu (Box 82)
        - I (Box 82)
        - IPR, Secretariat Bulletin (Transferred to IPR History)
        - J (Box 82)
        - Japan--Treatment of (Box 82)
        - Java Tiffin Club (Box 82)
        - Jayson, Alice (Box 82)
        - Jessup, Philip C. (Box 82)
        - Johnstone, William C. (Box 82)
        - Ka-Ke (Box 83)
        - Ki-Ko (Box 83)
        - Kizer, Benjamin H (Box 83)
        - Kr-Ku (Box 83)
        - L (Box 83)
        - Lattimore, Owen (Box 83)
        - Le (Box 83)
        - Lee, Rosamond (Box 83)
        - Li (Box 83)
        - Li, K.C. (Box 83)
        - Lo-Ly (Box 83)
        - Luce, Henry R. (Box 83)
        - Ma (Box 83)
        - Mayflower Hotel (Box 83)
        - Me (Box 83)
        - Me (Box 83)
        - Mi (Box 83)
        - Mitchell, Kate L. (Box 83)
        - Mo-Mu (Box 83)
        - Myers, Fred (Box 83)
        - N (Box 84)
        - Netherlands--Netherlands Indies Council (Box 84)
        - O (Box 84)
        - Office of War Information (Box 84)
        - Pa-Ph (Box 84)
        - Pacific Council
          - General (Box 84)
          - Conference Committee, 1944 April 22 (Box 84)
          - Minutes--Atlantic City, 1944 January 10 (Box 84)
        - Packard, Arthur W. (Box 84)
        - Parker, Philo W. (Box 84)
        - Philippines IPR. (Box 84)
        - Pi-Pu. (Box 84)
        - Porter, Catherine (Box 84)
        - Price, Ernest B. (Box 84)
        - Price, Harry B. (Box 84)
        - Q (Box 84)
        - Ra (Box 85)
        - Re-Ri (Box 85)
        - Revisions of Secretariat Report (Box 85)
        - Ro-Ry (Box 85)
        - Rockefeller Foundation
          - General (Box 85)
          - Willits, Joseph H. (Box 85)
        - Royal Institute of International Affairs
          - General (Box 85)
          - Macadam, Ivison (Box 85)
        - Russian War Relief (Box 85)
        - Sa (Box 85)
        - Sansom, George (Box 85)
        - Sch (Box 85)
        - Se (Box 85)
        - Sh (Box 85)
        - Si-Sl (Box 85)
        - Sm-Sp (Box 85)
        - Soong, T.V. (Box 85)
        - St (Box 85)
        - Staff Meetings (Box 85)
        - Stewart, Marguerite (Box 85)
        - Su-Sz (Box 85)
        - Sze, Sao-Ke Alfred (Box 85)
        - T (Box 86)
        - Tarr, Edgar J. (Box 86)
        - To (Box 86)
        - Trippe, Juan (Box 86)
        - Trone, S.A. (Box 86)
        - U (Box 86)
        - V (Box 86)
        - Wa (Box 86)
        - Wallace, Henry A.--Comments on "Our Job in the Pacific" (Box 86)
        - Walsh, Richard J. (Box 86)
        - Washington, D.C. Meetings (Box 86)
        - We (Box 86)
        - Welles, Sumner (Box 86)
        - Wh (Box 86)
        - Wi (Box 86)
        - Wo (Box 86)
        - X-Y-Z (Box 86)
        - Yardumian, Rose (Box 86)
        - Yen, Y.R.C. James (Box 86)
      - 1945
        - A-Am (Box 87)
        - American Council
          - Board (Box 87)
          - Executive (Box 87)
          - Finance (Box 87)
        - An-At (Box 87)
        - Austern, Hilda (Box 87)
        - Australian Institute of International Affairs (Box 87)
        - Ba (Box 87)
        - Bajpai, Girja Shankar (Box 87)
        - Be (Box 87)
        - Belshaw, Horace (Box 87)
        - Bi-Bl (Box 87)
        - Bisson, T.A. (Box 87)
        - Bo (Box 87)
        - Bolton, Frances P. (Box 87)
        - Br (Box 87)
        - Bu (Box 87)
        - Buck, Pearl S. (Box 87)
        - C (Box 88)
        - Canadian Institute of International Affairs (Box 88)
        - Carnegie Corporation (Box 88)
        - Carter, Edward C.
          - Notes of Talks (4 Folders) (Box 88)
          - Transcript of Press Conference (Box 88)
          - Notes of Speeches (4 Folders) (Box 88)
          - More Notes of Speechs (Box 89)
          - Bond Club Speech (Box 89)
          - Scripts and Speeches (Box 89)
          - Personal (Box 89)
        - Carter, Mrs. Edward C. (Box 89)
        - The Misses Carter (Box 89)
        - Carter, John A. (Box 89)
        - Carter, Margaret T. (Box 89)
        - Carter, Polly (Box 89)
        - Carter, William D. (Box 89)
        - Ce-Cl (Box 89)
        - Century Association (Box 89)
        - China Institute in America (Box 89)
        - China IPR (Box 89)
        - Co (Box 90)
        - Corbett, Percy E. (Box 90)
        - Corn Exchange Bank (Box 90)
        - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 90)
        - Cr (Box 90)
        - Da (Box 90)
        - Dafoe, J.W.--Copies of Letters by (Box 90)
        - De (Box 90)
        - Dennery, Etienne (Box 90)
        - Dennett, Raymond (Box 90)
        - Do (Box 90)
        - Dr-Du (Box 90)
        - E-Em (Box 90)
        - Emeny, Brooks (Box 90)
        - En-Ew (Box 90)
        - Fa-Fe (Box 91)
        - Fairbank, Wilma (Box 91)
        - Fairfax-Chomeley, Elsie (Box 91)
        - Farley, Miriam S. (Box 91)
        - Faymonville, Philip R (Box 91)
        - Fi (Box 91)
        - Field, Frederick V. (Box 91)
        - Field, Olga (Box 91)
        - Fisher, Galen M. (Box 91)
        - Fo-Fu (Box 91)
        - Foreign Policy Association (Box 91)
        - French Council, IPR. (Box 91)
        - Ga (Box 91)
        - Ge (Box 91)
        - Gelfan, Harriet Moore (Box 91)
        - Gi-Go (Box 91)
        - Gr-Gu (Box 91)
        - Grajdanzev, Andrew J. (Box 91)
        - Ha (Box 91)
        - He (Box 91)
        - Hersey, John--Dinner 24 April (Box 91)
        - Hi (Box 91)
        - Ho-Hs (Box 91)
        - Holland, W.L. (Box 91)
        - Hu (Box 91)
        - I (Box 92)
        - India (Box 92)
        - International Secretariat
          - General (Box 92)
          - Bulletin no. 13, 1945 March 24
            (Transferred to IPR History)
          - Bulletin No. 17, 1945 April 12
          - Union Organization (Box 92)
        - J (Box 92)
        - Japanese Psychiatrist Meetings (Box 92)
        - Java Tiffin Club (Box 92)
        - Jessup, Philip C. (Box 92)
        - Johnstone, William C. (Box 92)
        - Ka-Ke (Box 92)
        - Ki-Ko (Box 92)
        - Kirk, Grayson (Box 92)
        - Kr-Ku (Box 92)
        - La (Box 92)
        - Lasker, Bruno (Box 92)
        - Le (Box 93)
        - Li (Box 93)
        - Li, K.C. (Box 93)
        - Lo-Ly (Box 93)
        - Luce, Henry R. (Box 93)
        - Ma (Box 93)
        - Mayflower Hotel (Box 93)
        - Me (Box 93)
        - Me (Box 93)
        - Mi (Box 93)
        - Michael, Franz H. (Box 93)
        - Mitchell, Kate L. (Box 93)
        - Mo (Box 93)
        - Museum of Modern Art (Box 93)
        - Myers, Fred (Box 93)
        - N (Box 93)
        - Netherlands--Netherlands Indies IPR (Box 93)
        - New Zealand Institute of International Affairs (Box 93)
        - O (Box 93)
        - Office of War Information (Box 93)
        - Pa-Ph (Box 94)
        - Pacific Affairs (Box 94)
        - Pacific Council
          - General (Box 94)
          - Meeting Proposals (Box 94)
        - Philippine Institute of International Affairs (Box 94)
        - Pi-Pu (Box 94)
        - Pope, Arthur Upham (Box 94)
        - Porter, Catherine (Box 94)
        - Powell, Ifor B. (Box 94)
        - Ra (Box 94)
        - Re-Ri (Box 94)
        - Ro-Ry (Box 94)
        - Rockefeller Foundation
          - General (Box 94)
          - Willits, Joseph H. (Box 94)
        - Royal Institute of International Affairs
          - General (Box 94)
          - Macadam, Ivison (Box 94)
        - Sa (Box 95)
        - Salisbury, Laurence (Box 95)
        - Sansom, George (Box 95)
        - Sch (Box 95)
        - Schreiber, Julius (Box 95)
        - Se (Box 95)
        - Security in the Pacific (Box 95)
        - Sh (Box 95)
        - Si-Sl (Box 95)
        - Sm-Sp (Box 95)
        - Sta-Ste (Box 95)
        - Staff Meetings (Box 95)
        - Standard Practices and Policies, IPR (Box 95)
        - Stewart, Marguerite A. (Box 95)
        - Sti-Stu (Box 95)
        - Su-Sz (Box 95)
        - Ta-Th (Box 96)
        - To-Tw (Box 96)
        - Trippe, Juan (Box 96)
        - U (Box 96)
        - V (Box 96)
        - Wa (Box 96)
        - We (Box 96)
        - Wh (Box 96)
        - Wi (Box 96)
        - Wo-Wu (Box 96)
        - X-Y (Box 96)
        - Lardumian, Rose (Box 96)
        - Z (Box 96)
      - 1946
        - American Institute of Pacific Relations (Box 97)
        - American Russian Institute (Box 97)
        - An-Au (Box 97)
        - Australian Institute of International Affairs (Box 97)
        - Ba (Box 97)
        - Be (Box 97)
        - Belshaw, Horace (Box 97)
        - Bi (Box 97)
        - Bo (Box 97)
        - Borg, Dorothy (Box 97)
        - Br (Box 97)
        - Bu (Box 97)
        - Budget Sub-Committee (Box 97)
        - Ca (Box 97)
        - Canadian Institute of International Affairs (Box 97)
        - Carnegie Corporation (Box 97)
        - Ce-Cl (Box 97)
        - Chen Han-Seng (Box 97)
        - Chiang Mon-Lin (Box 97)
        - China IPR (Box 97)
        - Co (Box 97)
        - Comité d’Etudes des Problèmes du Pacifique (Box 97)
        - Corbett, Percy E. (Box 97)
        - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 98)
        - Cr (Box 98)
        - Da (Box 98)
        - De (Box 98)
        - Do (Box 98)
        - Dr-Du (Box 98)
        - Ea-Em (Box 98)
        - En-Ew (Box 98)
        - Fa-Fe (Box 98)
        - Fi-Fl (Box 98)
        - Field, Frederick (Box 98)
        - Fo-Fu (Box 98)
        - Foreign Policy Association (Box 98)
        - Ga (Box 98)
        - Ge (Box 98)
        - Gi-Go (Box 98)
        - Gr-Gu (Box 98)
        - Grajdanzev, Andrew J. (Box 98)
        - Ha (Box 98)
        - He (Box 98)
        - Hi (Box 98)
        - Ho-Hs (Box 98)
        - Holland, W.L.
          - General (Box 98)
          - Personal (Box 98)
        - Hu (Box 98)
        - I (Box 98)
        - International Secretariat
          - General (Box 98)
          - Bulletin, 1946-1949
          - Inquiry Fund (Box 98)
          - Staff (Box 98)
        - International Studies Conference--Mayoux, J.J. (Box 98)
        - J (Box 99)
        - Jessup, Philip C. (Box 99)
        - Ka-Ke (Box 99)
        - Ki-Ko (Box 99)
        - Kr (Box 99)
        - La (Box 99)
        - Lattimore, Owen (Box 99)
        - Le (Box 99)
        - Li (Box 99)
        - Li, K.C. (Box 99)
        - Lilienthal, Philip E. (Box 99)
        - Liu Yu-Wan (Box 99)
        - Lo (Box 99)
        - Loomis, Charles F. (Box 99)
        - Ma (Box 99)
        - Mayer, Adrian (Box 99)
        - Me (Box 99)
        - Me-Mi (Box 99)
        - Michael, Franz H. (Box 99)
        - Mo-Mu (Box 99)
        - N (Box 99)
        - Netherlands Council, IPR (Box 99)
        - New Zealand Institute of International Affairs (Box 99)
        - O (Box 99)
        - P (Box 99)
        - Pacific Affairs (Box 99)
        - Pacific Council
          - General (Box 99)
          - Budget (Box 99)
          - Finance (Box 99)
        - Philippine Council, IPR (Box 99)
        - Pi (Box 99)
        - Porter, Catherine (Box 99)
        - Progress Toward Self-Government in Dependent Areas (Box 99)
        - Q (Box 99)
        - Ra-Re (Box 100)
        - Research--IRC Reports, Minutes, etc. (Box 100)
        - Ro-Ru (Box 100)
        - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 100)
        - Royal Institute of International Affairs (Box 100)
        - Sa (Box 100)
        - Sc (Box 100)
        - Sh (Box 100)
        - Si (Box 100)
        - Sm-Sp (Box 100)
        - Southeast Asia Institute (Box 100)
        - St (Box 100)
        - State Department (Box 100)
        - Su-Sw (Box 100)
        - Ta-Th (Box 100)
        - Tarr, Edgar J. (Box 100)
        - To-Ty (Box 100)
        - U (Box 100)
        - United Nations (Box 100)
        - V (Box 100)
        - Wa (Box 100)
        - We (Box 100)
        - Wh (Box 100)
        - Wi (Box 100)
        - Wo-Wy (Box 100)
        - X-Y-Z (Box 100)
- Part II. American Institute of Pacific Relations, 1926-1959 and Miscellaneous Committee Files
  - American Institute of Pacific Relations, Miscellaneous
    - Carter, Edward C.--To Board of Trustees (Box 101)
      - 1947 April 16 (Box 101)
      - 1947 May 20 (Box 101)
      - 1947 May 23 (Box 101)
    - Coronado Resolution
      - Correspondence (Box 101)
      - Original Replies (Box 101)
    - Earle, Edward Meade (Box 101)
    - Emeny, Brooks (Box 101)
    - Foreign Policy Association (Box 101)
    - Gardner, Charles S. (Box 101)
    - Gelfan, Harriet Moore (Box 101)
    - Jessup, Philip C. (Box 101)
    - McConaughy, James L. (Box 101)
    - Meetings--Executive Committee; Board of Trustees (Box 101)
    - Norem, Ralph A. (Box 101)
    - Notestein, Ada Comstock (Box 101)
    - Rademaker, John A (Box 101)
    - Suehsdorf, Alfred (Box 101)
    - Welles, Sumner (Box 101)
    - American IPR--Miscellaneous (Box 102)
    - Chamberlain, Joseph P. to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Coons, Arthur G. to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Durdin, F.T. to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Elliston, Herbert (Box 102)
    - Fisher, Galen W. (Box 102)
    - Fisher, H.H. to Clayton Lane (Box 102)
    - Hansen, O.C. to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Herod and Toynbee (Box 102)
    - Lane, Clayton (with extract of letter from Arnold J. Toynbee) (Box 102)
    - Lattimore, Owen to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Mackay, James A. to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Mimeographed Testimonials (Box 102)
    - Murphy, J. Morden to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Parker, P.W. to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Sinclair, Gregg M. to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)
    - Sproul, Robert Gordon to Carnegie-Corporation of New York (Box 102)
    - Taylor, George E. to Ray Lyman Wilbur (Box 102)